To match the effect of Hanfu, I first made a simple hairstyle with a版 of the original version.
I used a stabilizer to fix it close to the head, and then copy a layer as the outer layer of the hair.
The outer layer of the hair should be larger, so that it can be inflated and bulge like a hair bun.
To increase the bending strength of this panel, reduce the wrinkle, and make the fabric more flexible.
Reduce the strength of the gold tail sand and the corner line sand, because the fabric is more stretched, and it can expand more after being inflated.
Increase the pressure of the outer layer to 50, so that the hair bag can be inflated.
The principle of shaping the hair bag is to divide a rectangular panel into two sides.
The bending strength needs to be increased to 100, because the fabric is very hard, it is not easy to collapse, and it forms a tube.
After making the panel, select all the panels that form the hair at the window of the second level.
And then select that which is selected by DolbingJ.
In this way, you can only Ungle of all selected items to OBJ.
In the sectuation, the most important thing is the couple setting.
First of all, you can choose to unagle all the items as many targets,
or unagle one.
When unagleing, you can choose does it contains thickness.
In the previous choice, you can choose not to técce thicknessksen the flight,
You can choose whether to align the line along the line or parallel to the board.
Next, let's take a look at the effect of different settings.
The first one is for multiple targets.
With this kind of offset setting, the boards will be independent of each other into one area,
and there will be no grid on the back of the side and no thickness overall.
The second one is for multiple targets.
With this kind of offset setting, the boards will be independent of each other and the thickness will be offset.
The boards will be independent of each other and no thickness overall.
Due to the fact that the grid on the side of the current software cannot be edited and there is no UV,
the UV on the side will be lost when the thickness is offset, and it needs to be edited later.
The third one is for multiple targets.
The boards will be divided into different types of fabrics, and each type of fabric will be divided into one area.
When there is a seam line between the boards,
the two sides of the boards will be aligned at the top of the seam line.
the boards will be aligned at the top of the seam line.
The combination option can only be applied when you select thin.
The example shown here is that the thickness is thin when you select one target and the combination can be eliminated.
After the combination is eliminated, there is a seam line throughout the board,
but the boards no longer coincide with the top.
When you choose the represent for thickness,
you cannot choose the combination option because there is a grid in the side of each board.
You will see that the whole area is selected at the same time.
Open HANA, and you can see that there is also a hair.
The hair will be turned into a virtual model, and the selection of the loading type will be increased.
After selecting the hair, you can use the positioning ball to move its position or transform it.
After displaying the texture, you will see that the side texture of the version just disappeared.
In the current version, the side grid is not UV, so the texture will be clearly lost.
Let's temporarily set the side texture to single color.
Then adjust the other parts as well.
Let's move the texture to the desired color.
Now select the hair.
Change the color of the hair to the desired color to adjust it.
Select the side and then adjust the hair to the desired color.
At first, I will do the same technique as before.
Next, select the hair and then adjust the subject to the selected color.
At the time of selection, the color is suddenly changed by the properties selected.
Let's change the color.